welcome welcome uh my name is Delan
Grant and uh this is uh uh my second uh
presentation on man life I was um hoping
I do hope that you are able to review
the first slide on 2016 okay name of
insurance company for B Mobility this is
uh for shortterm disability is man life
insurance which is located in montal
Quebec Canada this was not my first
experience in man life and I discovered
that manone life is not for the
employees it's actually for the company
okay all right man life insurance
company did me wrong before and they did
the same thing again all right and I'm
short giving you my presentation here
please feel free to pause and read if
I'm going too fast okay thank
you damages as I said myy life is
responsible for everything that happened
in my life there after there are after
to cover up their deception including
murder attempts yes okay so
2017 it was a year it was uh a lot of
activities a year with lot of activities
regarding my situation so I have put it
in two parts part one and part two so
I'm going to go deal with part one right
now thank
you the medical system delayed my
recovery as
2016 okay I have went through um 2016
okay I was sent back to work in my
condition after I saw Dr James Chang on
August 8 2016 2 months right um two
months with injury okay um eventually
diagnosed with Deen citis I was off work
effected September 7 2016 Dr James Chang
had made no recommendations or of a
referral to see a specialist for my
injury injured right hand 3 months later
not three my my my hand was now in his
uh third month right Dr James Chang did
not complete a Form 8 required by law a
Form 8 yeah I didn't know about that
right at the time um I knew of this
through wsib uh visited the office of Dr
James Chang on September 15 2016 to
complete the bc935 form this form is for
man life insurance and was informed that
I would be contacted with a date to see
a specialist okay two weeks later I
contacted the officer Dr James Chang
about the specialist but was told that
they had been unsuccessful we went
through that okay and I have to wait and
the physiotherapy we went through all
that okay um it says here
um this the last time in 2016 on my
previous presentation it we left off
where I visited Dr James sh's office on
December 13th and was told that I um an
appointment was scheduled to see Dr
handman right for June 26 2017 okay this
further delay my recover uh my recovery
right because um I had to
wait April 2017 oh this is another
section this there I say a lot of
activities went on within 2017 so we'll
get there further theat my recovery
April 2017 to December 2017 8 months
without physiotherapy we will get there
all
right okay so after waiting for 4 months
to see a specialist from September to
January remember now my injury is now in
its sth month 7 month and 11 days I had
this injury so when I saw doctor
Handelman the rheumatologist he
indicated positive falstein test as you
can see here okay please refute to read
okay and then um I'm thanking God for
Great Lakes Medical cuz if it wasn't for
great lak medical I would not have had
an ultrasound done so he was able to
make mention of the clinically supported
ultrasound evidence of inflammation
right and in the um drct hesman I think
at the time to me he seemed like a nice
person um when he his letter started to
say thank you for asking me to see Mrs
Grant she's a pleasant year old um
whatever married ra right-handed female
who works as who works at Bell okay um
Dr andman there's some information here
I can't recall he made making mention
about stopping to fysio and all that I
can't recall maybe it did but I can't
recall however um was
planning an uh for me to attend um sod
Brook Hospital to have the C cortisol
injection administered okay I um as he
indicated here um that I will arrange a
repeat ultrasound okay all right and if
there's evidence of information
ultrasound guided czone injection
followed by splint
the next 5 to 7 days that is if I get
the um the cortisone injection right um
so as you can see went to him on 26th of
January 2017 and I received a
requisition for son Brook Hospital okay
please feel free to pause and read and
feel free to pause and read okay I
thought I was in good hands at the time
please feel
free to pause and read thank you
then I was being forced back to work by
man life insurance man life insurance
would I have it I was off work here and
um December 31st man life insurance sent
me a letter stating that I should return
the week of February 6 be free to pause
and read then on February 2nd right
second um sent to Dr Handelman right
letter stating that I should return to
work the week of February 6th Dr handman
said no okay I was being sent to
Sunnybrook Hospital for the cortisone
injection and my appointment was
February 15th okay please ref you to
pause and
read I received this record from Dr
handman and I can read I can read Sun
Brook hospital and the um the recession
was from Dr handman as you can see here
Sam handman okay physician who referred
me and I'll give you a better view on
the next page the next slide okay the P
febrary 15 and it did say
if if um
okay if inflamed inject if inflamed on
febrary 15 attended appointment at Sun
Brook Hospital for the cortisone
injection Deus confirmed there was no
inflammation the injection was not given
as per instructions on the recogition um
also the the doctor explained the reason
why she did not administer the injection
I did not refuse injection there was no
fluid right there was no fluid so the
doctor I saw did the radiograph the r
the radiologist did not um administer
the injection as per the requisition
please feel free to read if you can I'll
give you a better view
okay a better view of the requisition I
got from Dr Handelman and it
says ultrasound of the right thumb AB
doctor extensor tension seat and if
inflamed inject inject with the c own
injection if inflamed I went there for
the injection uh okay on February 15th I
saw dror and this man on the 26th of
January this when I got the requisition
okay if inflamed inject and it means
what the the um radi the radiologist
explain um inflame means um if there's
fluid that's why that's what's causing
the pain you know severe pain okay
please feel free to pause and read
her findings was that I still had deavan
tenis and aitis there was no fluid as
she said right right Dr provin provin
did not administer the injections there
the date the date that I went to
Sunbrook hospital please feel free to
pause and read thank
you in the
meantime the clinical notes of quality
care clinics bam G
all right was still being distorted okay
dou bless I be taking over from man life
insurance in the LA bigr Jeet say I need
to provide false clinical notes I will
get to that when I go to dou SI ib's
presentation okay but just to show you
here on the 15th I went to um um Sun
Brook hospital and he wrote here on the
17th of February feeling
better okay my attendance were still
soen and in pain but the pain was not as
severe like when it just started in
September okay I was icing my hands at
home doing the extra while I was at home
okay I wanted to get better all right
please be free to pause and read
thanks
Dr money life insurance again contacted
Dr
hesman right
on February 23rd I I I brought this one
forward just for you to compare so um
for the February 2nd as you can see this
was what the email the letter looks like
right but on the 23rd of February there
were some
inclusions as you can see right the
inclusions were one highlighted here
please note that in order to um approve
the absence on short-term disability
benefits the employee has to be
considered as totally disable from
performing her job task despite the
accommodation offered by the employer
and
two return to work the week of ma March
7th 2017 and three here working at a
slower Pace allowing the employee to
work with her left hand only Dr
Handelman responds no
okay
okay my life would have it so I I I was
actually on the day of March 7th there
was a I was supposed to be reassessed
the man life sorry Sunny Brook Hospital
I sent the the results to Dr hesman Dr
hesman knew that I was not capable in
returning to work in my condition
however Word of Mouth he said I should
return to work use my hand I will be off
work again I knew my workplace I did not
agree but you know I didn't contest this
was his decision so I returned to work
and but and he sent a letter to man life
stating that um the above patient is um
can return to work the week for the week
of whatever March 13 okay I got this
letter from that written by Dr hesman
and I got it um I think the lad part of
the year when I realized the deception
so although he told me Word of Mouth his
report stated otherwise he said that I
was better in a three weeks he said um
this was done on February 15 cuz I did
the ultrasound right and it says the
ultrasound did not reveal tendon sheet
information to Warrant ACC own injection
right she remained off work cuz I said
inflammation if there was inflammation
then the injection would be would have
been administered but there was no
inflammation so I did not need the
injection right
what he said today she has a negative
fingerin test Dr Dr hesman did not
examine me that day it did not perform
any
examination right and um and he said
here that I I had no swelling e no
swelling wow so to cover himself no
swelling he indicated here and please
feel free to read if you can okay but
this report was in favor of man life
okay as you can see when I returned to
work on March 15
2017 right SW in hand
okay it's swen up to my
elbow and here's a picture of what de
ten is
okay luckily you see God God knew what
he was doing E I did not realize that I
was actually putting my case together so
on the 15th of March I took this picture
was taken by one of my coworker
okay man life
agreed um you see bability actually
agreed with man life insurance that I
should use my left hand to
work yeah my left hand to work so I I
actually returned on March 15th then
there the uh just the work
facilitator came in and uh and to
reassess my um desk and all that and and
her you know although she was from man
in life this this um person um had
Integrity Angela Miss Angela yes I had
Integrity she recorded she listened and
recorded the right information my my my
notes were not misc conscrew at all she
provided the correct information okay
okay be for free to pause and read this
was March um this was done in March 16
2017 okay at Bell in mitag
okay work facilitation
meeting the Miss Angela I would say call
her right recorded location 5099 Creep
by Mrs Saga okay and this was March 16
and she said Miss Grant has been working
for B Mobility about about 19 years and
in her current position for a little
less than a year right some some some
others recorded that I was I it was all
my life I was working as a customer
service rep but she was really she
listened and she provided the correct
information however I am just you please
refuse to read I'm just going to point
out here when she said at the time of
the assessment she has pain at the risk
that is much more intense on the thumb
side and that radiates up to the Elbow
she she was watching me typing and
whatever right and all that the pain
remains some the sorry the area sorry
remains somewhat swollen now on on in Dr
hesman report on March 17 said said
there was no more swelling yet as you
can see from the picture on March 15th I
had swelling and here the assessor um
stated that I do have sweating and still
pain all right um it says she had been
told to get an elastic brace to
stabilize the area and the thumb but it
seemed nobody made sure she got the
right one not even the physiotherapist
right I got I still had a wrong brace I
tell you please of you to pause and read
thank
you the same day that um I was assessed
um at Bell Mobility to be
ergonomically set up and all that right
and as cessa also recorded that had
swelling and you know that was uh um
March 15th and also have a picture of
March 15th with my hand the selling on
my hand okay all the that all those
information yet um on the 15th of March
2017 here's a letter from Quality Care
from B Ram G the physiotherapist stating
that um swelling is no more okay I had
asked um Quality Care Bri Ramjet for uh
letter which I would wanted to give to
wsib which is
workplace workplace safety insurance
board okay because I was denied I was
denied so I've been asking B PR G since
February it has now been March okay and
uh he decided to do the report on March
16 and decided to lie so as I said my
clinical notes were being distorted
because of man life and wsib and um he
indicated assess again on March 15 2017
swelling is no more okay so when I
returned um for physio the following
week on March 22nd right that was when I
saw this and I I and you know what he
did he gave it to me at the end so
luckily I read it right there I read it
right there but he was nowhere to be
found he left the building totally maybe
he went for lunch I don't know but he
was not in the building when I was
leaving this this the receptionist which
I haven't seen for a while right she
said Hi and then she asked me about my
hand and I showed it to her she said oh
it's still soen and I I sarcastically
said oh can you see
that okay so I then I showed her letter
and then she said oh no he has to change
this he has to change it right so
um yes and I saw him on the day all
right um I had I
um as a matter of fact um the date
hasn't changed but I left the letter on
this date March 22nd I left the letter
with her so he had to change it he had
to change at some point in time I what I
did I went in on another day to retrieve
the cor correction but still not um
pleased because um he was
deceitful yeah so he indicated their
swelling significantly reduced I could
not trust him again with my health no no
okay um I did not return to the clinic
okay and I guess because I did not he
wrote for the 22nd as if he had
completed his mission then in helping me
to get better so because it was my last
day I decided I'm not returning to
Quality Care this is what he wrote
patient is in no pain today
huh I tell you so please feel free to
pause and read that what this is what
the medical system does to people here
many people the the amount of people
mental issue and is not that they want
to it's a system the system allow them
many many some may be just like natural
but many like this if I didn't know God
I tell you the system basically tried to
mess up just to cover for B Mobility
please refute to pause and read okay
thank
you I attended another physiotherapy
Clinic the follow the following day yeah
you know luckily I did I tell you March
23rd
2017 um I went to Bramton Physiotherapy
and wellness Institute okay life
clinics and they
wrote on the 23rd as you can see 23rd of
March 2017 and Bramton Physiotherapy and
wellness Institute and they wrote Deen
citis severity worse it worse at nine
out of 10 but best five out of 10 okay
um feel free to pause and read and see
here quality Care 22nd of March and I
went to Bramton physio on the 23rd of
March okay and they have it here they
can see the swelling so they Circle it
right risk
okay and they indicated that I had I had
of intens since July I guess you know
cuz the pain started in June and the
swelling appeared in July
okay um they I brought this again okay
just to show you the 23rd of March 2017
23rd of March 2017 and they actually
indicated here the physiotherapist right
thumb m
R swelling so the swelling was there
okay benefit sees abruptly on April te
no more physiotherapy left on my own by
the medical doctor since my return to
work the i byb in February 2017 R
nicolini Law Firm for my WSB claim on
April 10 2017 I decided to visit Dr
James Chang in May 2017 to recommend a
new specialist I did I I I you know um
because I was left on my own actually
right I was the N of Dr James Chang I
was told to contact Dr Sam handers Man's
office for an appointment since I was
still within the year right referal was
still valid
okay here I did
um for for
um W IB because I was denied I obtained
a
lawyer from the Yan nicolini Law Group
right this is retainer just a one page
this this is nothing this just a
signature so just a one page contract
okay and it says workplace safety and
insurance board I know we're dealing
with man life but this is also important
right um um so I retain the lawyer on
April 10 2017 please feel free to pause
and read
okay and there's part two of um the
presentation on uh for 2017 okay
thanks